[{"answer": " Do I look like I'm not all right", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Were you really worried about me or your stupid dinner was getting cold", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Subconscious??  Meaning it was all motivated by truth that came out under the influence of alcohol", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "And what kind of commendation would you expect for being a loyal German", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "But you said other Germans... What OTHER Germans...  Who are they?  Why aren't they loyal?  Who", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Why?  You're not drinking... you said you weren't responsible last night because you were drunk!  Are you drunk now", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "HELMUT ", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You're not a religious man, are you, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You're wasting your time.  He doesn't perform for the likes of us... he'll turn you down", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "And, of course, the BIG heads of that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The Commandant thinks you are", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "They'll get over it.  Disappointment is no stranger to those children", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm sure they have", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " I wish they'd get them out of here. Prison is no place for little children", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " You're right!  I've got to think of myself", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You want to talk to the children? Well, I think I can help you", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Reason?  When war is waged against children!  That is reason enough for the whole damn world to get involved. And it will, believe me, it will", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " my friend is going to talk to the children. Cover him", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " The Reverend says cover him... so we cover him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I know.  I know.  But the siding isn't far from town.  The General doesn't want unauthorized persons getting curious.  Understand", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Men!  You'll get yourself down there. And take at least a dozen guards with you.  Don't let anyone get close to that boxcar...  under any circumstances.  No one ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Out of the question.  The man's being disciplined for that very thing.  We can't change our position now", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He'd know", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Of course.  That way she can't get lost, can she?  What's her name", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Where are they sending us", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Do you have children", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We're moving.  What's happening? What was the noise?  my friend, where are we going", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Is it far?  Are you coming, too?  I don't want a train ride", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " It's nothing.  You're going for a train ride.  What do you think of that?  A real train ride", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, it'll be fun.  I would like to come, but I don't think I can", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Where are we", "docId": "Day-the-Clown-Cried_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I... I'm from the other prison.  Got locked in", "qsentId": 34}]